Guide to the The Writer's Center records, 1978-2006 MS2232
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
The Writer's Center records
1978-2006
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
MS2232
4 Linear Feet
This collection contains issues of the Carousel from 1978-2005, workshop brochures from between 1986-2002 and Poet Lore from 1978-2006.
Restrictions on Access
Some records may be restricted.
Acquisition Information
Donated in 2007
Historical or Biographical Note
Founded in 1976, the Writer's Center is a non-profit community of writers supporting each other in the creation and marketing of literary texts. The Writer's Center annually conducts hundreds of workshops in various genres of writing. The Writer's Center also hosts literary events, readings and conferences; sells books and literary magazines
The Writer's Center is housed in a 12,200 square foot facility in the arts and entertainment district of Bethesda, Maryland, with workshops also offered in Leesburg and Arlington, Virginia, and at other locations around the greater Washington, D.C., metropolitan area.
Collection Scope and Content
This collection contains issues of the Carousel from 1978-2005, workshop brochures from between 1986-2002 and Poet Lore from 1978-2006.
This collection is not yet processed, please see staff for assistance.
Collection Organization
This collection is not fully processed and series have not yet been identified.
Poetry -- Workshops; Washington (D.C.); Writer's Center (Bethesda, Md.)
- Carousel, 02/1978 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Carousel, 03/1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Carousel, 04/1978 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Carousel, 07/1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Carousel, 09/1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Carousel, 05/1979 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Carousel, 06/1979-07/1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Carousel, 12/1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Carousel, 02/1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Carousel, 03/1980 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Carousel, 09/1980 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Carousel, 12/1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Carousel, 02/1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Carousel, 04/1981 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Carousel, 03/1981 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Carousel, 06/1981 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Carousel, 09/1981 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Carousel, 06/1986-07/1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Carousel, 01/1991-02/1991 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Carousel, 02/1991-03/1991 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Carousel, 05/1991-06/1991 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Carousel, 07/1991-08/1991 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Carousel, 11/1991-12/1991 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Carousel, 01/1992-02/1992 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Carousel, 07/1992-08/1992 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Carousel, 1980-1993 (Box 3)
- Carousel, 1994-2005 (Box 4)
- Workshop brochure, 1986, Spring (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Workshop brochure, 1986, Summer (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Workshop brochures, 1991, Winter (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Workshop brochures, 1991, Spring (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Workshop brochures, 1991, Summer (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Workshop brochures, 1992, Spring (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Workshop brochures, 1993, Winter (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Workshop brochures, 2002, Winter (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Conference pamphlette, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Poet Lore vol. 75 #1, 1980, Spring (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Poet Lore vol. 75 #2, 1980, Summer (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Poet Lore vol 75, #3, 1980, Fall (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Poet Lore vol 75, #4, 1981, Winter (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Poet Lore vol 76, #1, 1981, Spring (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Poet Lore vol 76, #2, 1981, Summer (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Poet Lore vol 76, #3, 1981, Fall (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Poet Lore vol 76, #4, 1982, Winter (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Poet Lore vol 77, #1, 1982, Spring (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Poet Lore vol 77, #2, 1982, Summer (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Poet Lore vol 77, #3, 1982, Fall (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Poet Lore vol 77, #4, 1983, Winter (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Poet Lore vol 78, #1, 1983, Spring (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Poet Lore vol 78, #2, 1983, Summer (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Poet Lore vol 78, #3, 1983, Fall (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Poet Lore vol 79, #1, 1984, Spring (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Poet Lore vol 79, #2, 1984, Summer (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Poet Lore vol 79, #3, 1984, Fall (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Poet Lore vol 79, #4, 1985, Winter (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Poet Lore vol 80, #1, 1985, Spring (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Poet Lore vol 80, #2, 1985, Summer (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Poet Lore vol 80, #3, 1985, Fall (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Poet Lore vol 80, #4, 1986, Winter (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Poet Lore vol 81, #1, 1986, Winter (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Poet Lore vol 81, #2, 1986, Summer (Box 1, Folder 59)
- Poet Lore vol 81, #3, 1986, Fall (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Poet Lore vol 81, #4, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Poet Lore vol 82, #2, 1987, Summer (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Poet Lore vol 82, #3, 1987, Fall (Box 1, Folder 63)
- Poet Lore vol 82, #4, 1987, Spring (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Poet Lore vol 82, #4, 1987-1988, Winter (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Poet Lore vol 83, #1, 1988, Spring (Box 1, Folder 66)
- Poet Lore vol 83, #2, 1988, Summer (Box 1, Folder 67)
- Poet Lore vol 83, #3, 1988, Fall (Box 1, Folder 68)
- Poet Lore vol 83, #4, 1989-1990, Winter (Box 1, Folder 69)
- Poet Lore vol 84, #1, 1989, Spring (Box 1, Folder 70)
- Poet Lore vol 84, #2, 1989, Summer (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Poet Lore vol 84, #3, 1989, Fall (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Poet Lore vol 84, #4, 1989-1990, Winter (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Poet Lore vol 85, #1, 1990, Spring (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Poet Lore vol 85, #2, 1990, Summer (Box 1, Folder 75)
- Poet Lore vol 85, #3, 1990, Fall (Box 1, Folder 76)
- Poet Lore vol 85, #4, 1990-1991, Winter (Box 1, Folder 77)
- Poet Lore vol 86, #1, 1991, Spring (Box 1, Folder 78)
- Poet Lore vol 86, #2, 1991, Summer (Box 1, Folder 79)
- Poet Lore vol 86, #3, 1991, Fall (Box 1, Folder 80)
- Poet Lore vol 86, #4, 1991-1992, Winter (Box 1, Folder 81)
- Poet Lore vol 87, #1, 1992, Spring (Box 1, Folder 82)
- Poet Lore vol 87, #2, 1992, Summer (Box 1, Folder 83)
- Poet Lore vol 87, #3, 1992, Fall (Box 1, Folder 84)
- Poet Lore vol 87, #4, 1992-1993, Winter (Box 1, Folder 85)
- Poet Lore vol 88, #1, 1993, Winter (Box 1, Folder 86)
- Poet Lore vol 88, #2, 1993, Summer (Box 1, Folder 87)
- Poet Lore vol 88, #3, 1993, Fall (Box 1, Folder 88)
- Poet Lore vol 88, #4, 1993, Fall (Box 1, Folder 89)
- Poet Lore vol 89, #1, 1994, Spring (Box 1, Folder 90)
- Poet Lore vol 89, #2, 1994, Summer (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Poet Lore vol 89, #3, 1994, Fall (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Poet Lore vol 89, #4, 1994-1995, Winter (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Poet Lore vol 90, #1, 1995, Spring (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Poet Lore vol 90, #2, 1995, Summer (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Poet Lore vol 90, #3, 1995, Fall (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Poet Lore vol 90, #4, 1995-1996, Winter (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Poet Lore vol 91, #2, 1996, Summer (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Poet Lore vol 91, #3, 1996, Fall (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Poet Lore vol 91, #4, 1996-1997, Winter (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Poet Lore vol 92, #1, 1997, Spring (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Poet Lore vol 92, #2, 1997, Summer (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Poet Lore vol 92, #3, 1997, Fall (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Poet Lore vol 92, #4, 1997, Winter (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Poet Lore vol 93, #1, 1998, Spring (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Poet Lore vol 93, #2, 1998, Summer (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Poet Lore vol 93, #3, 1998, Fall (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Poet Lore vol 93, #4, 1989-1999, Winter (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Poet Lore vol 94, #2, 1999, Summer (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Poet Lore vol 94, #3, 1999, Fall (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Poet Lore vol 95, #2, 2000, Summer (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Poet Lore vol 95, #3, 2000, Fall (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Poet Lore vol 95, #4, 2000-2001, Winter (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Poet Lore vol 96, #1, 2001, Spring (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Poet Lore vol 96, #2, 2001, Summer (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Poet Lore vol 96, #3, 2001, Fall (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Poet Lore vol 81, #1/2, 2003, Spring (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Poet Lore vol 97, #3/4, 2002, Fall-Winter (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Poet Lore vol 98, #1/2, 2003, Spring-Summer (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Poet Lore vol 98, #3/4, 2003, Fall-Winter (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Poet Lore vol 99, #1/2, 2004, Spring-Summer (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Poet Lore vol 99, #3/4, 2004, Fall-Winter (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Poet Lore vol 100, #1/2, 2005, Spring-Summer (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Poet Lore vol 101, #3/4, 2005, Fall-Winter (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Poet Lore vol 101, #3/4, 2006, Fall-Winter (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Poet Lore vol 101, #1/2, 2006, Spring-Summer (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Open Door: A Poet Lore anthology, 1980-1996 (Box 2, Folder 37)